<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tips on Jason Corns&#39; blog...</title>
    <link>http://www.jasoncorns.com/tags/tips/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tips on Jason Corns&#39; blog...</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>All rights reserved, 2011-2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2010 20:08:33 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.jasoncorns.com/tags/tips/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Semantic Css Establishing a Visual Outline</title>
      <link>http://www.jasoncorns.com/2010/08/semantic-css-visual-outline/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2010 20:08:33 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jasoncorns.com/2010/08/semantic-css-visual-outline/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s move beyond simply linting our code, and delve into creating a visual outline of our CSS. Anyone who writes code, anything from simple UI shifts through complex exotic joins, inherits a responsibility to write reasonable code. Good code solves a problem or answers a question; well-written code lives on, open and accessible to future developers.
Before we begin, let me say that the delivered stylesheet should be minified and free of excess spaces, tabs, semicolons and lengths of 0px instead of “0″, using tools like the YUI compressor or the CSS Drive Online CSS Compression Utility.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accessibility Series, pt. 1</title>
      <link>http://www.jasoncorns.com/2010/04/accessibility-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2010 20:21:11 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jasoncorns.com/2010/04/accessibility-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Usability is finally starting to bubble to the top for Web Designers and Information Architects. We are, as an industry, starting to realize that our audience exists outside of Photoshop canvas and beyond the code. In fact, I have witnessed an increased focus on JavaScript degradation over the past few months – an unspoken admission that we, as web design professionals, should and shall provide web content to users of all browsing backgrounds and capabilities.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>